I took the supermarket flowers from
the windowsill
Threw the day old tea from the cup
Packed up the photo album Matthew
had made
Memories of a life that’s been loved
Took the get well soon cards and
stuffed animals
Poured the old ginger beer down
the sink
Dad always told me don’t you cry
when you’re down
But mum there’s a tear every time
that I blink
Oh I’m in pieces it’s tearing me
up but I know
A heart that’s broke is a heart
that’s been loved
So I’ll sing Hallelujah,
You were an
angel in the shape of my mum
When I fell down you’d be there
holding me up
Spread your wings as you go
And when
God takes you back
He’ll say Hallelujah, you’re home
I fluffed the pillows, made the
beds, stacked the chairs up
Folded your nightgowns neatly
in a case
John said he’d drive, then put his
hand on my cheek
And wiped a tear from the side
of my face
I hope that I see the world as you
did cause I know
A life with love is a life that’s
been lived
So I’ll sing Hallelujah,
you were an
angel in the shape of my mum
When I fell down you’d be there
holding me up
Spread your wings as you go, when
God takes you back
He’ll say Hallelujah, you’re home
Hallelujah,
you were an angel in the
shape of my mum
You got to see the person that
I have become
Spread your wings and I know
That when
God took you back, he said
Hallelujah you’re home